# KIRILL LUNEV Software developer

email: lmar521@mail.ru phone: 053-438-4484 WA: +79242666787

linkedin: linkedin.com/in/kirill-lunev

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a oleh hadash from Russia and I am looking for a job in Israel. In Russia, I have been engaged in management accounting automation and development for more than 10+ years. Conducting projects for the implementation and maintenance of corporate information systems. I also have competencies in the field of formalization and writing of technical tasks, and formalization of customer requirements into functional requirements for the system. I am experienced 1C developer with more that 50 projects in my portfolio. Now I am a junior Java developer and looking for my next job to continue develop my skills and bring my expertise to the team

#### **SKILLS**

- Problem-solving
- SQL, 1C, basic Java
- Teamwork
- Formalization of business requirements
- Independent learning Project management

## WORK EXPERIENCES

- SOFTWARE DEVELOPER / SMALL BUSINESS OWNER Jun 2013 - up to present | Self-employed
  - Implementation of accounting and management automation projects in various companies. 50+ different projects
  - Trained programmers for my team. I have trained 3 entry-level programmers for my team.
  - Various integration projects using various technologies and formats (json, api, http sockets, xml, webhooks)
- SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Oct 2012 - May 2013 | DNS | One of the largest electronic companies in Russia. More than 1,000 stores, more than 10,000 employees

- Revision of existing and development of new mechanisms of working configurations of the company (Two configurations developed from scratch, Accounting of the enterprise)
- Optimization of existing mechanisms, reports, and treatments.
- Setting and monitoring the execution of tasks by other programmers (2 subordinate)
- Finding and correcting accounting errors
- SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Apr 2011 - Sep 2012 | Prodis | Large distribution company, 500+ employees

- Database Administration.
- Configuring the configuration for the needs of users.
- Independent technical support of a dedicated accounting automation unit
- Consulting accountants and users on emerging issues
- JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Sep 2010 - Apr 2011 | Iterra | Software implementation and Maintenance company

- Revision of standard IC configurations, updating configurations, writing reports/treatments, correcting errors, advising users.
- Automation of business processes based on 1C:CRM for LLC "Aiterra".
- Creating a sales manager's desktop for a trading company.

#### **EDUCATION**

2007 - 2011 | VLADIVOSTOK STATE UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS AND SERVICE **B.A in Applied Computer Science** 

## INTERESTS

- Boxing, work-out, books and films